Muhammad Umer

Full Stack Developer

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 3+ years of related experience.



Work History

Address

Faisalabad, 37250

Phone

+923456013122

E-mail

mumer119131@gmail.com



Web Frontend



Development

Web Backend



Development

Python Django



Python Selenium



MongoDB

Excellent

Android Application

Development (Java)

Excellent

React ••

Python Tkinter



Very Good

Python Flask



2022-04 - Full Stack Developer

Freelancer, Faisalabad

- Consulted with engineering team members to determine system loads and develop improvement plans.
- Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- Developed unit test cases for testing and automation.



2022-07

Education

2019-09 -Current Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

University of Agriculture Faisalabad - Pakistan

2022-05 -Current Diploma: Web And Mobile Application Development

Sylani Mass IT Training Center - Faisalabad